{
  "theme": [
    {
      "Questions": [
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the main ship in 'Futurama'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Planet Express Ship",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Death Star",
            "Millennium Falcon",
            "Starship Enterprise"
          ],
          "Explanation": "The Planet Express Ship is a delivery spacecraft used by the crew in the animated series 'Futurama'. It has a distinct appearance with its eye-like shape and accounts for the main mode of transport in the show."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which character is known for saying 'I have the power' in 'He-Man'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "He-Man",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Skeletor",
            "She-Ra",
            "Beast Man"
          ],
          "Explanation": "He-Man, also known as Prince Adam, is the protagonist of 'He-Man and the Masters of the Universe'. He utters 'I have the power' to transform into the powerful He-Man."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the robot companion in 'The Jetsons'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Rosie",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "R2-D2",
            "Bender",
            "C-3PO"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Rosie is the robotic maid in the futuristic cartoon 'The Jetsons'. She provides comedic relief and assistance to the Jetson family in their daily lives."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which animated series features a character named Bender?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Futurama",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Rick and Morty",
            "The Jetsons",
            "Transformers"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Bender is a foul-mouthed, heavy-drinking robot and a central character in 'Futurama'. His sarcastic and mischievous personality offers humor throughout the series."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the teenage girl who pilots the giant robot in 'Neon Genesis Evangelion'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Asuka Langley Soryu",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Rei Ayanami",
            "Shinji Ikari",
            "Misato Katsuragi"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Asuka Langley Soryu is a skilled pilot and part of the main cast in the anime 'Neon Genesis Evangelion'. She operates the Evangelion Unit-02 and brings a confident and competitive spirit to the storyline."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'Transformers', who leads the heroic Autobots?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Optimus Prime",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Megatron",
            "Starscream",
            "Bumblebee"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Optimus Prime is the noble and courageous leader of the Autobots in the 'Transformers' universe. His iconic presence and sense of justice drive the resistance against the evil forces of the Decepticons."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is Marsupilami's favorite catchphrase in the animated series?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Hoobah",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Smurfy",
            "Zoinks",
            "Flame On"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Marsupilami, a fictional yellow-spotted animal, frequently utters 'Hoobah' in the animated series. The catchphrase reflects the character's exuberant and playful nature."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which animated series follows the adventures of a boy named Hiro?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Big Hero 6: The Series",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Ben 10",
            "Gravity Falls",
            "Teen Titans"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Hiro Hamada is the main protagonist in 'Big Hero 6: The Series'. The show continues the story of the film 'Big Hero 6', focusing on Hiro's experiences as a member of the superhero team."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Who is the arch-nemesis of the ThunderCats?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Mumm-Ra",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Skeletor",
            "Megatron",
            "Shredder"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Mumm-Ra, an ancient and powerful sorcerer, is the primary antagonist in 'ThunderCats'. He constantly seeks to defeat and conquer the ThunderCats and possesses formidable dark magic."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which animated series features a character named Zapp Brannigan?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Futurama",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "The Jetsons",
            "Invader Zim",
            "Voltron"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Zapp Brannigan is a flamboyant and inept space captain in 'Futurama'. His overconfident and clueless demeanor contributes to comedic situations within the show."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the powerful fighter in 'Dragon Ball Z'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Goku",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Naruto",
            "Luffy",
            "Vegeta"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Goku, also known as Kakarot, is the main protagonist of 'Dragon Ball Z'. As a Saiyan, he possesses immense strength and is driven by a relentless desire for self-improvement and protecting the Earth."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which animated series features the character Megabyte?",
          "TrueAnswer": "ReBoot",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Code Lyoko",
            "Voltron",
            "Cyberchase"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Megabyte is the primary antagonist in the computer-animated series 'ReBoot'. His manipulative and intelligent nature presents a continual threat to the digital world of Mainframe."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the robot companion in 'The Jetsons'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Rosie",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "R2-D2",
            "Bender",
            "C-3PO"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Rosie is the robotic maid in the futuristic cartoon 'The Jetsons'. She provides comedic relief and assistance to the Jetson family in their daily lives."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'Transformers', what type of vehicle does Bumblebee transform into?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Car",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Truck",
            "Jet",
            "Tank"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Bumblebee transforms into a small yellow compact car in the 'Transformers' series. This vehicle form provides agility and versatility during battles and reconnaissance missions."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which animated series follows the adventures of a boy named Hiro?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Big Hero 6: The Series",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Ben 10",
            "Gravity Falls",
            "Teen Titans"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Hiro Hamada is the main protagonist in 'Big Hero 6: The Series'. The show continues the story of the film 'Big Hero 6', focusing on Hiro's experiences as a member of the superhero team."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which cartoon includes a cyborg detective named Major Motoko Kusanagi?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Ghost in the Shell: Stand Alone Complex",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Scooby-Doo",
            "The Flintstones",
            "The Powerpuff Girls"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Major Motoko Kusanagi is a key character in 'Ghost in the Shell: Stand Alone Complex'. As a cyborg, she leads Section 9 in combating cybercrime and existential threats in a futuristic world."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Who is the intelligent and resourceful inventor in 'Inspector Gadget'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Penny",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Brain",
            "Gadgetmobile",
            "Claw"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Penny, the niece of Inspector Gadget, is a skilled inventor and detective in the animated series. She often assists her uncle in solving crimes and outsmarting the villainous Dr. Claw."
        },
        {
          "Question": "In 'Voltron: Legendary Defender', which paladin pilots the Red Lion?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Keith",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Lance",
            "Pidge",
            "Hunk"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Keith is the fiery and bold pilot of the Red Lion in 'Voltron: Legendary Defender'. Together with his teammates, he forms part of the mighty Voltron to protect the universe from evil forces."
        },
        {
          "Question": "Which animated series features a character named Zorak?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Space Ghost Coast to Coast",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "The Jetsons",
            "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",
            "Scooby-Doo"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Zorak, a villainous mantis, is a regular character in 'Space Ghost Coast to Coast'. He serves as the bandleader and often engages in banter with the show's host, Space Ghost."
        },
        {
          "Question": "What is the name of the half-human, half-gem protagonist in 'Steven Universe'?",
          "TrueAnswer": "Steven",
          "FalseAnswer": [
            "Greg",
            "Pearl",
            "Garnet"
          ],
          "Explanation": "Steven is the central character in 'Steven Universe'. As a hybrid of a human and a gem, he embarks on adventures while learning about his powers and navigating complex relationships."
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}